Your Site for Freebies and More!

#### Press ESC to close

 Search

Privacy Policy
==============

_Privacy Notice_
================

**Last Updated on Dec 3rd, 2024**

**OKWOW.COM PRIVACY NOTICE — IMPORTANT — PLEASE READ**

This website is operated by OK WOW (“OK WOW,” “We,” “Us,” or, “Our”).  This privacy notice (the “Privacy Policy”) discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for the OK WOW website, mobile applications, electronic services, and social networking sites (collectively, the “Site”). We provide this policy to help you understand how we treat the information collected and how such information is used and shared.

Please note that by using this Site and our services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree with the terms described in this Privacy Policy, please do not provide us with your personal information or interact with the Site.

Please also review our [Terms of Use](https://okwow.com/terms/), which govern your use of the Site and the ​Privacy Policies of our Third Party Advertisers, should you choose to sign up for any of their offers.

**WHAT INFORMATION IS OBTAINED?**

**User Provided Information** – When you register with us or use the Site, you may provide us certain information voluntarily. This may include: (a) your name, mobile or residential phone number, zip code, e-mail address, postal address, date of birth, gender, answers to survey questions, and other registration information; (b) responsive information, such as when you enter into sweepstakes or respond to any offers; (c) information you provide us when you contact us; (d) information you enter into our system when using the Site, such as contact information which is clearly labeled at the time you submit it; and (e) information you post on our Site. We collect this information from you in order to provide you with the Services described within our Site and to deliver you newsletters, orders, or other information or services as requested.

**Automatically Collected Information** – When you use the Site, we automatically collect certain information from you, such as Internet addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring and exit page, operating system, timestamps, clickstream data, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device’s unique device ID, the IP address of your mobile device, and your mobile operating system. We also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers. This information is logged and used for purposes such as to help diagnose technical problems and to administer our Site so that we can constantly improve it.

**Cookies.** Cookies are small data files placed in your browser. Cookies transmit information such as session ID, user ID, and conversion data. This information helps website providers recognize a browser or mobile device and helps us gather information such as how many users have visited our site and which pages and advertisements have been seen and clicked on. We use first-party cookies and third-party cookies together to report ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with ad impressions related to your visit to our Site.  Such information is used to tailor your experience on our Site.

**Third-Party Analytics.** We may collect certain information via third-party analytics services that may collect your non-sensitive user information. This may include: the information you provide us, your session ID, your user ID, your interest data, and conversion data. These third parties may collect hashed user data directly from emails or communications using cookies, web beacons, or other similar technologies on behalf of OK WOW and/or for companies with no common ownership marketing purposes.  This information provides us with tools to calculate the numbers and frequency of visitors on the Site and to understand how you and other users use the Site so to improve your experience.

**Google Analytics.** We enable Google Analytics to support Display Advertising. We have implemented the following Google Analytics features to support Display Advertising: Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. You may opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network advertisements at [http://www.google.com/settings/ads](https://www.google.com/settings/ads)

* _Remarketing with Google Analytics._We use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the Internet. Both ourselves and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our website.
* _Google Display Network Impression Reporting and DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration._Both ourselves and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our site.
* _Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting._ We use data from Google’s Interest-based advertising or third-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) with Google Analytics to match you with the right message and show you advertisements that are more relevant to your interests.

**Data Providers and Internet-Based Advertising.** We may work with data providers and third-party advertisers who may collect web log data from you (including IP address and information about your browser or operating system), place, or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads, personalized e-mail or content.  Such cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information but reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to the data you voluntarily submitted to us (e.g. your e-mail address that is shared solely in hashed, non-human readable form).

**HOW IS THE COLLECTED INFORMATION SHARED?**

We use the information that we collect for several purposes including: to provide our services, send you samples or offers that you request, contact you regarding new promotions, improve our Site, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our customer agreements.  We limit how we share this information with others and only share sensitive information, such as phone numbers, when you provide explicit consent for us to share that information.  Below is a description of the ways we use and/or share the information you share with us based on the different types of data.

Phone number:  We treat phone numbers and phone-related data as sensitive information and, as such, only share it with others when you provide explicit, clear, and conspicuous consent for us to share that information.  In those instances where you agree to allow us to share your phone number with others, we only share that information with the company or companies you grant permission for us to share that with.  This is done during the survey section of the registration where you may see one or more advertisements based on your answers to the survey questions presented to you when you register.  For us to share your phone number, you must respond by clicking “Yes” at the bottom of the advertisement of the third party, where a clear and conspicuous disclosure is presented confirming the phone number you agree to share as well as the company(s) you agree to share your phone number with.  The phone data is ONLY shared with the third party when you explicitly agree to share that by clicking “Yes”. You can see an illustration of this opt-in process here:

When you register with us or use the Site, you may provide us with your mobile telephone number for the specific purpose of being contacted via telephone calls or text (SMS) messages.  When you provide us with your mobile number and check the box to sign up for text message updates and offers, you are providing us with your consent to receive automated phone calls or text messages from or on behalf of OK WOW, some of which may be conducted via an automatic dialing system.  Further, you understand that consent is not required as a condition of purchase.

We do not charge you for receiving mobile text messages, but message and data rates may apply from your mobile carrier or service provider.  Your mobile carrier may collect data about your wireless device usage.  Any charges from your mobile carrier or data collection by your mobile carrier are governed by your mobile carrier’s policies and not by our terms.  We may collect data in connection with the text messaging service, including your name, mobile number, mobile service provider or carrier’s name, and any other information you may provide us.  This information is used to contact you and provide the services as described within.  OK WOW is not liable for any undelivered messages or delays of text messages.

We might also use your phone number in an encrypted form of matching to verify if you have a current business relationship with another company.

No mobile information will be shared with third parties/affiliates for marketing/promotional purposes. All the above categories exclude text messaging originator opt-in data and consent; this information will not be shared with any third parties unless you explicitly consent to share your information with those companies.

**IT IS IMPORTANT TO NOTE THAT, UNLESS YOU EXPLICITLY OPT IN AND AGREE TO RECEIVE SMS TEXT MESSAGES OR PHONE CALLS FROM OK WOW, ADVERTISERS, OR OTHER PARTIES, WE DO NOT TRANSFER, LICENSE, OR SHARE YOUR PHONE INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES FOR THE PURPOSE OF UNSOLICITED SMS MESSAGING OR PHONE CALLS.**

**Emails & Newsletters.** When submitting any information on our website you will see a disclaimer for receiving emails from OK WOW, companies owned by the same legal entity as OK WOW, and third-party advertisers. You expressly authorize OK WOW, and its Associated Entities to use your personal information as explained in this privacy policy, and you consent to receiving commercial email from them as well. You can expect to receive offers regarding specific products and/or services, newsletters, sweepstakes announcements, promotions, and other similar offers.

**We might utilize your email address for the purpose of recognizing you upon your next visit to our website and/or to send you our newsletter and promotional ” OK WOW ” emails if you provided it and selected the option to receive it. You can unsubscribe from our emails at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email you receive. We will not share your email with anyone else unless explicitly permitted by the terms outlined in this Privacy Policy and your express consent.**

**Direct Mail and Survey Data.** We may use the information we collect directly, indirectly, and in combination with data we share with other parties, to introduce you to informational, service, and/or product offerings of OK WOW and/or its subsidiaries, companies owned by the same legal entity as OK WOW, companies with no common ownership, third-party advertisers, assigns, and/or brands that are owned by, licensed by, and/or partnering with [okwow.com](https://okwow.com/) (collectively, “Associated Entities”) via direct mail. We do this by transferring, licensing, and/or sharing your information with Associated Entities so they may correspond with you and provide you with marketing materials and/or promotions that may be of interest to you via direct mail. Associated Entities may also transfer, and/or share your information with subsequent third parties that may want to advertise other products and/or services. This implies that once a third party obtains your information, its use is/will be controlled by the privacy policies and terms of use of that third party. Direct Mail and Survey Data sharing do NOT include email or phone number data unless you explicitly consent to sharing that information.

**Third-Party Advertisers.** We work with several Third-Party Advertisers and may share some of your information with these Third-Party Advertisers to provide you with the best deals and offers available that we believe will be of interest to you. You may see any of these Third-Party Advertisers’ ads or offers on the Site or on websites, applications, and services operated by the Third-Party Advertisers. When signing up for the Site, you may be asked to complete a survey.  You may be shown a Third-Party Advertisers’ offer while completing the survey.  You may choose to skip any offer shown to you or you may choose to provide your information in response to the offer.  When you respond to any offer shown, we will transfer some or all the information that you submit during the website registration process to the Third-Party Advertiser. Once a Third-Party Advertiser receives the information you submit to them, their use of your information is controlled by the privacy policy of that third party.     

**Data Disclosure and Transfer: Legal Obligations:** We may also share your information in response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; when we believe disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of our company, our employees, our web site users, or others; or to enforce our website terms and conditions or other agreements or policies. We may also transfer any data we collect in connection with a corporate change such as a merger, our acquisition by another company, or a partial or total sale of our assets (including as part of a bankruptcy proceeding).

**WHO DO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH?**  
We share your information with the following entities for the purpose of either getting postal data, direct mail, or data support. This does not include phone data. We do NOT share your phone data without your explicit consent.

* Data Axle – postal data
* Net60 – postal data
* NetSpend – postal dataLightfoot Media Inc. – direct mail
    * Affordable Health Options
    * Cross Country Mortgage
    * Loan Depot
    * TrustedConsumer.com
    * US Disability Partner

**WHAT ARE MY OPT-OUT RIGHTS?**

Here at OK WOW, we value the choices of our users and thus, we provide options for you to opt out of certain services that you no longer wish to use and options regarding the information you have shared with us, depending on the service as listed below:

* _OK WOW_ _Newsletter_: You may unsubscribe by clicking the “Unsubscribe” link in the email you receive. You may also unsubscribe by sending an e-mail to [\[email protected\]](https://okwow.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). Please allow up to ten (10) days for us to process your unsubscribe request.  
    
* _Mobile Communications_. If you no longer wish to receive telephonic communications via your mobile device, you may unsubscribe at any time by texting “**STOP**” in response to the message(s) you receive.  You may receive a confirmation message or further instructions on how to completely unsubscribe if you have registered to multiple mobile offers.  You may also text “**HELP**” in response to the message(s) you receive to get more information.  
    
* _Do Not Track_: At this time, when we collect information from you for the purpose of tracking your online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services, we do not respond to “Do Not Track” signals or frameworks requesting an alteration to our online tracking of individual users who visit our Site or use our services.  
    
* _Third Party Advertising_: Our Site and newsletters may include third party advertising and links to other websites. We may work with third-party advertising networks and advertisers who help deliver these ads to you and who may collect information about your browsing activity over time and across different sites in order to make this advertising more relevant. Some of those ads may be personalized, meaning that they are intended to be relevant to you based on information we or the online advertising network collects about your online activities here and elsewhere over time. Although you may not opt out of receiving online advertisements generally, you may control the collection of data on our Site used for targeted okwow.com advertising during your visits to other websites. To opt out of these types of ads, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative for information about how to opt-out of interest-based advertising by their members. See [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) for general information about the NAI and [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt\_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) for the opt-out page. You may also visit [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) to learn more about Internet-based advertising by third parties and [http://www.aboutads.info/consumers/](http://www.aboutads.info/consumers/)to learn about choices available and how to opt-out from online behavioral ads served by some or all participating companies.  
    Please note that if you do choose to opt-out from third-party behavioral advertising, you will still receive advertisements, but they will not seem as relevant to you and your interests.  In addition, note that if you use a different browser or erase cookies from your browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice.  
    
* _Google Analytics_: You may opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network advertisements at www.google.com/settings/ads

**STATE DATA PRIVACY RIGHTS**

Some states have enacted data and/or privacy laws that apply to the residents of those states.  These state laws provide you with specific legal protections and restrict how we use and share your information with others.  Below is a list of the state laws in effect at the time this Privacy Policy was updated.

### **California**

If you are a resident of California, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information.  We may make your personal information available to third parties for their marketing purposes, as described in this Privacy Policy. We maintain the policy of only disclosing such personal information to third parties with your affirmative consent.

The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), along with its amendments through Proposition 24, the California Privacy Rights Act (CPRA), empowers consumers by granting them rights to control their personal information held by businesses. These rights include knowing what information is collected, deleting it, opting out of its sale, and protection against discrimination for exercising these rights. The CPRA introduces additional rights, such as correcting inaccurate information and limiting the use of sensitive data.

Businesses under CCPA have responsibilities like responding to consumer requests and providing privacy notices. Penalties range from fines to potential damages for breaches, potentially reaching significant amounts for actions affecting consumers. It is important to add that the CPRA amends the CCPA; it is not a different law.

_What are your rights?_ To access, delete, correct your data, obtain a copy of your information, and to opt-out of the sale/share of your information.

### **Connecticut**

The Connecticut Data Privacy Act (CTDPA), which came into effect on July 1, 2023, gives consumers control of their data and provides them with rights such as access to, correction of, and deletion of personal data, as well as the ability to opt out of data sale and processing.

The CTDPA applies to companies operating in the state as well as those targeting Connecticut residents, with specified data volume and revenue requirements. It imposes obligations on data controllers, including the requirement to limit data acquisition, maintain security procedures, and acquire consent. Sensitive data, such as racial, health, and genetic information, requires express opt-in consent.  The Connecticut Attorney General is in charge of enforcing the CTDPA, which carries fines of up to $5,000 per infraction.

The law is being implemented in stages, with companies given a grace period until January 1, 2025, after which more challenging compliance is required. Additionally, beginning in 2025, companies must provide consumers with a uniform opt-out method for targeted advertising and data sale.

_What are your rights?_ To access, delete, correct your data, obtain a copy of your information, to opt-out of the sale/share of your information and targeted advertising.

### **Virginia**

On January 1, 2023, the Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act (VCDPA) came into full effect in Virginia. Its main aim is to enhance consumer protection in the digital space. This act introduces broader privacy rights, defines personal information comprehensively, establishes protection for sensitive data, and sets data protection standards for those handling data. The VCDPA applies to businesses operating in Virginia or targeting its residents and handling personal data of a certain volume or deriving a significant portion of revenue from such data. However, certain entities like those under HIPAA, not-for-profits, and financial institutions are exempt. The act requires businesses falling under its scope to conduct and document data protection assessments, enforced by the Virginia Attorney General’s office with fines for violations reaching up to $7,500 each.

_What are your rights?_ To access, delete, correct your data, obtain a copy of your information, to opt-out of the sale/share of your information and targeted advertising.

### **Colorado**

The Colorado Privacy Act grants rights to residents over their data and imposes responsibilities on data controllers. Businesses must comply with notice requirements, obtain consent for certain data processing, conduct data protection assessments, and fulfill data subject access requests (DSARs). The CPA provides five main consumer rights: opt-out, access, correction, deletion, and data portability. It applies to businesses collecting data from a certain number of Colorado residents. Small businesses have exemptions, but penalties for violations under the CPA can be up to $20,000 per offense, capped at $500,000, enforced by the Colorado Attorney General without a private right of action.

_What are your rights?_ To access, delete, correct your data, obtain a copy of your information, to opt-out of the sale/share of your information and targeted advertising.

### **Utah**

The Utah Consumer Privacy Act (UCPA), effective from Dec. 31, 2023, marks Utah as the fourth state with comprehensive consumer privacy legislation. It resembles laws from Virginia, Colorado, and California but takes a more business-friendly approach. Its scope covers entities meeting specific revenue thresholds and processing data of a certain number of consumers. The Act provides fewer rights compared to other state laws, focusing on access, deletion, data portability, and opting out of specific processing. It excludes certain data types and grants exemptions to various entities, offering narrow enforcement and no private right of action.

_What are your rights?_ To access, delete, correct your data, obtain a copy of your information, to opt-out of the sale/share of your information and targeted advertising.

### **Texas**

Texas passed a new law called the Texas Data Privacy and Security Act (TDPSA) which will become effective on July 1, 2024. This law affects how companies handle people’s personal information in Texas. It’s similar to laws in Virginia and California.

The TDPSA applies to almost any business in Texas or selling to Texans that handles personal data. Personal data now includes not just obvious information like names and addresses but also online usernames or other data that could identify a person.

Small businesses are mostly exempt, unless they sell sensitive data like health information, in which case they need permission first. Companies must be transparent about how they use personal data and must protect it from being misused. They must also limit the amount of data they collect to what’s really needed for their purposes.

Texans now have more control over their data. They can ask companies to show them what data is being collected, correct any mistakes, or even delete their data. They can also choose not to have their data used for targeted advertising or be sold to other companies.

The law also has rules for companies that process this data, making sure they follow the same guidelines as the companies collecting it.

_What are your rights?_ To access, delete, correct your data, obtain a copy of your information, to opt-out of the sale/share of your information and targeted advertising.

### **Oregon**

The Oregon Consumer Data Privacy Act (OCDPA) is about how companies can use and protect your personal information. It will become effective on July 1st, 2024. The OCDPA is similar to laws in other states and gives people in Oregon more control over their personal data.

The OCDPA applies to businesses that operate in Oregon or offer products or services to people in Oregon. The law requires businesses to be clear about what personal data they collect and why, and to only collect what they really need. Businesses must also protect personal data and reduce the risk of harm to consumers.

Consumers in Oregon have rights under the OCDPA. They can ask businesses to show them the personal data collected, correct it if it’s wrong, delete it, or get a copy of it. Parents or guardians can also do this for their children. The law also protects sensitive data, like health information or information about a person’s race, and requires businesses to get permission before using it.

The OCDPA does not let businesses sell personal data without permission. Businesses must give consumers an easy way to say no to selling their data. The law also has rules for how businesses can use personal data for targeted advertising, making sure it’s done in a fair and transparent way.

_What are your rights?_ To access, delete, correct your data, obtain a copy of your information, to opt-out of the sale/share of your information and targeted advertising.

**For Oregon consumers, you may submit your privacy requests via email, to the following address** [\[email protected\]](https://okwow.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)**. Please include a valid government-issued ID, your full name, and your address. The information provided must match our records in order for us to process your request.**

### **Montana**

The Montana Consumer Data Privacy Act is a law that makes sure companies are honest about how they use people’s personal information in Montana. If a company does business in Montana or sells products or services to people in Montana, and they handle a lot of personal information from Montana residents, this law applies to them. However, it doesn’t apply to government agencies, schools, or certain types of personal information like health records or research data.

Under this law, Montana residents have the right to know if a company is using their personal information and can ask for a copy of their data or have it corrected or deleted. They can also choose not to let a company use their data for things like targeted ads or selling it to others. Companies must also keep personal data safe and not discriminate against people who exercise these rights. They have to explain clearly in a privacy policy how they use personal data and give people an easy way to contact them about privacy concerns.

Companies must be careful with sensitive data like genetic information or precise location data, and they can’t sell sensitive personal information to third parties without permission. Companies must assess the risks of their data processing activities and make sure that data is de-identified if it’s shared. If a company uses another company to handle data for them, they must have a contract in place to ensure data is protected. Finally, if a company violates these rules, the Montana Attorney General can investigate and take action, but the company has a chance to fix the problem first.

_What are your rights?_ To access, delete, correct your data, obtain a copy of your information, to opt-out of the sale/share of your information and targeted advertising.

### **Nevada**

Nevada’s privacy law, known as the Nevada Privacy of Information Collected on the Internet from Consumers Act (NPICICA), focuses on regulating how websites and online service providers collect and handle personal information of Nevada residents. Enacted in 2017, this law requires operators of commercial websites and online services to post a clear and conspicuous privacy notice. This notice must inform consumers about what personal information is being collected, how it will be used, and whether it will be sold or shared with third parties. Operators are also required to provide a designated request address for consumers to exercise their rights under the law, such as opting out of the sale of their information.

In summary, the Nevada privacy law gives consumers the right to opt-out of the sale of their personal information to third parties, which is a significant element of privacy protection. Operators must act on these requests and must not discriminate against consumers who choose to exercise their rights under the law.

_What are your rights?_ To opt-out of the sale/share of your information. However, we do not sell personal information.

### **Vermont**

In the absence of a specific statewide privacy law, Vermont residents have to refer to the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA) for healthcare-related privacy and the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) for the online privacy of children under 13. Also, Vermont has data breach notification laws that ask companies to notify individuals and the Vermont Attorney General’s office in the event of a data breach.

_What are your rights?_ To opt-out of the sale/share of your information. However, we do not sell personal information.

If you want to submit a request for privacy rights, please send it in writing to the following address: 

OK WOW  
Attn: Legal Department  
3131 W Bolt St  
#A19  
Fort Worth TX, 76110  
[\[email protected\]](https://okwow.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)  
  
or make an online request here:  

**VISUAL PLAYBACK TECHNOLOGY**

We use third-party technology to validate what is presented to you and the actions you take while on our Site.  This technology provides a “visual playback” from the third party that confirms these actions along with other data points such as geo location of the user that took the actions, the IP address on the device they used, the time and date stamp of the visit and each action taken, and the keystrokes to validate the information you share with us.  The services we use for Visual Playback are [Verisk’s TCPA Guardian](https://marketing.verisk.com/docs/tcpa-guardian) (formerly known as Jornaya’s LeadID) and [Active Prospect’s Trusted Form](https://activeprospect.com/trustedform/auto-retain/?utm_source=Website&utm_medium=Marketing-CPC&utm_term=&utm_content=&utm_campaign=Google-CPC-US-PMax-Acquisition-Lead-TF&match_type=&device=c&utm_id=19019739781&gad_source=1&gclid=CjwKCAiAs6-sBhBmEiwA1Nl8s9PpDgdG_kWGP3LQOKtA-qU4y_a8BDqcu0es-rOs3TgTbiWJbxdfohoCJ28QAvD_BwE). 

**DATA RETENTION POLICY**

We will retain user-provided data for as long as you use the Site and for a reasonable time thereafter. If you’d like to access, update, or delete User Provided Data that you have provided via the Site, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://okwow.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or the address below and we will respond in a reasonable time. Before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies, or delete any information, however, we may ask you to verify your identity. Please note that some or all of the User Provided Data may be required in order for the Site to function properly, and we may be required to retain certain information by law.

**SECURITY**

We take reasonable and appropriate measures to help prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of your information by carefully limiting access to the database in which your personal information is stored. Even though we follow reasonable procedures to try to protect the information in our possession, no security system is perfect and we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that your information will be secure in all circumstances.

**CHILDREN**

The Site is not directed to children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from someone under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records.

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES**

Our Site may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours.  We do not have control over the information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.  You should consult the privacy policy of these other sites to learn how your privacy is protected.

**YOUR CONSENT**

Please note that by using the Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the practices described in this Privacy Policy, please do not provide us with your personal information or interact with the Site. Your assent to these practices is essential for us to continue operating this website, including the services it provides. Similarly, we need you to provide accurate personal information so that you can be contacted and receive the information you request. You can opt out and decide not to provide the requested personal information. However, by doing so, you will not receive the information and/or service you are requesting.

**CONTACT US**

To reach the owner of this website, contact:

OK WOW  
3131 W Bolt St  
#A19  
Fort Worth TX, 76110  
[\[email protected\]](https://okwow.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY**

We may make modifications to this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any material changes, we will notify you of such changes by posting the new policy on the Site or by sending you an e-mail. If you continue to use the Site after modifications, your continued use will constitute as acceptance of the changes and you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. Review our Privacy Policy regularly so that you can stay informed of our practices, as they may change in the future.

Ezoic Services
==============

Ezoic Services  
This website uses the services of Ezoic Inc. (“Ezoic”), including to manage third-party interest-based advertising. Ezoic may employ a variety of technologies on this website, including tools to serve content, display advertisements and enable advertising to visitors of this website, which may utilize first and third-party cookies.  
A cookie is a small text file sent to your device by a web server that enables the website to remember information about your browsing activity. First-party cookies are created by the site you are visiting, while third-party cookies are set by domains other than the one you're visiting. Ezoic and our partners may place third-party cookies, tags, beacons, pixels, and similar technologies to monitor interactions with advertisements and optimize ad targeting. Please note that disabling cookies may limit access to certain content and features on the website, and rejecting cookies does not eliminate advertisements but will result in non-personalized advertising. You can find more information about cookies and how to manage them [here](https://allaboutcookies.org/).  
The following information may be collected, used, and stored in a cookie when serving personalized ads:

* IP address
* Operating system type and version
* Device type
* Language preferences
* Web browser type
* Email (in a hashed or encrypted form)

Ezoic and its partners may use this data in combination with information that has been independently collected to deliver targeted advertisements across various platforms and websites. Ezoic’s partners may also gather additional data, such as unique IDs, advertising IDs, geolocation data, usage data, device information, traffic data, referral sources, and interactions between users and websites or advertisements, to create audience segments for targeted advertising across different devices, browsers, and apps. You can find more information about interest-based advertising and how to manage them [here](https://youradchoices.com/).  
You can view Ezoic’s privacy policy [here](https://ezoic.com/privacy/), or for additional information about Ezoic’s advertising and other partners, you can view Ezoic’s advertising partners [here](https://www.ezoic.com/privacy-policy/advertising-partners/).

### Table of Contents

Don’t Be Strangers
------------------

Sign up to get daily giveaways, and more!

### Quick Links

### Quick Links

**This website or its third-party tools process personal data. You can opt out of the sale of your personal information by clicking on the “Do not Sell or Share my Personal Information" link [here](https://okwownewstg.wpenginepowered.com/#).** The third-party product names, logos, brands, and trademarks shown on this website are the property of their respective owners. These companies are not affiliated with OkWow. These third parties do not sponsor or endorse this website, its content, or services.  
Copyright © 2024.  OkWow is a registered trademark of Tibrio LLC.

[Open toolbar Accessibility Tools](javascript:void(0); "Accessibility Tools")

Accessibility Tools
